FILING FOR LOVE
What kind of dream was that?
Did you get some rest?
Don't forget to come in
at the usual time today. Good luck.
Oh, right. Work.
No wonder I had that terrible dream.
Here's your iced Americano.
Mr. Noh.
- Are you okay now?
- What do you mean?
When there was a ruckus outside
two days ago
you passed out in shock.
The photos are everywhere.
They call you the Haemu Fainter.
I heard the affair was real.
So her husband is
Mr. Son from Food Brand Planning?
What happens to them now?
You handle the employees' affairs...
- Da-yeong.
- Yes?
I think your orders
are pretty backed up.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, Mr. Noh.
The Haemu Fainter.
You look fine. Are you all right now?
- I'm fine.
- Good.
I heard you're in charge of affairs.
How did that happen?
- I thought you were some big shot.
- Hey.
I handle PM cases, not affairs.
And the term is
"personal misconduct."
You're just clueless.
Mr. Noh.
Yes, Ms. Park.
I heard what happened.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
That's good to hear.
Hey, there, Mr. Noh.
Are you just clocking in?
I'm so pleased to see you,
I could faint.
Ms. Joo.
You can't tease me about that.
Why not? Don't I have the right?
The only reason you're fine
without a single scratch
is that I caught you like this
with my two arms as you fell.
You know I saved you, right?
I sprained my wrist a bit,
so I got some acupuncture.
Sure, I can't thank you enough.
It's nothing, really.
I'll type up a report on what action
to take against Mr. Son.
I took care of that already.
What?
I closed that case.
Mouthwatering and mellow,
here's Masigo.
With Haemu's own
innovative food technology
Masigo succeeded to realize
the farm-to-table notion
and we're confident it will become
a brand that represents Haemu
and leads global food trends.
That concludes the presentation.
Thanks for listening.
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
Even so, that's not right, Ms. Joo.
How could Ms. Jeong be demoted
to a plant while Mr. Son remains?
And he gets to keep his project?
If we must decide who did worse,
Ms. Jeong is single
while Mr. Son's married,
so he did more harm.
Who did Mr. Son cause harm to?
Mr. Son always did well at work
and he's in charge of a new brand
the Food Team has invested in.
What about Ms. Jeong?
All she did was play a part
in Mr. Son's project.
Her performance and reputation
are below his.
From the company's point of view
Ms. Jeong has done more harm
than Mr. Son.
Am I wrong?
Still, morally speaking...
Morals?
Do you think
you're a police officer or a judge?
Do companies reward the good
and punish the bad?
A company only has to care
about the profit or loss
caused by an employee.
Because here,
that is our ethics and morals.
What is it?
Did you hope
for an exhilarating resolution?
For a cheating couple
to be humiliated out of their jobs?
You're more naive than you look.
Why did you put me in charge?
This duty
doesn't suit me because I'm naive.
No, you're perfect for the job.
- Ms. Joo, what on earth...
- Don't get too upset.
Mr. Son got a bigger percentage
of his pay docked.
Not to mention that this incident
ruined his reputation for good.
It will be taken into consideration
at his next performance review.
Plus, there are legal repercussions
if he's sued for divorce.
There, let's forget
about a closed case.
Do your next assignment right.
Sorry?
"Work.com."
You should check it out.
The comments are insane.
EPISODE 2:
I AM THE BEST
Seriously, do something about Zone F.
It's basically a love motel in Haemu.
- It's like watching porn.
- "Zone F"?
So everyone knows it.
The head office's
basement parking lot.
- It probably has no cameras.
- What is this about?
I never park there.
Is this news to you?
It's Zone F in level four
of the basement parking lot.
It's the spot
for couples in the company
whether they're dating
morally or immorally.
It's dark with no cameras
pointing that way
and not many park that far down.
It's perfect.
You seem to know a lot, Mr. Cha.
That's what I heard
through the grapevine.
Let's check the facts first.
We can't investigate
based on a rumor.
- Yes, sir.
- Okay?
Check facts? With whom?
Our team has set up
- a humint network.
- What? "Humint"?
INFO GATHERED FROM INFORMANTS
- Yes.
- Gosh, don't even talk about it.
There's no end to it.
It's embarrassing for both parties
if we catch them in the act.
We just turn a blind eye.
I heard Zone F is the place to go.
BASEMENT PARKING CLOSED
FOR REPAIR WORK
It's that spot over there.
Is it more thrilling
if they do it there?
I don't know why people
with decent jobs would do that.
I wonder myself.
If you see anything suspicious
please report it to us.
- Sure thing. Take care, then.
- Thank you.
Our humint network confirmed
the rumor is true.
Humint, my foot.
- Let's go eat.
- Okay.
The cafeteria's serving pork cutlet,
doenjang soup
- braised potatoes...
- Not there.
I'll check my list
of nearby restaurants.
Don't bother.
THIS EVENING
What are you doing today?
It's your birthday.
Did your boyfriend schedule a date?
Well...
Why are you so mysterious?
I'm curious what kind of guy
girls like you date.
Why does the cafeteria food
get worse by the day?
- Right? Let's eat out tomorrow.
- Okay.
- Ms. Yeon.
- What?
Isn't that Mr. Kwon, your husband?
Yes, that's right.
Why don't you even say hi?
Did you two fight?
We didn't fight. We get along fine.
Ji-yeon, wait until you get married.
After just a few years
you flinch
when your hands accidentally touch.
That's an exaggeration.
You two are hilarious.
Before you got married,
you didn't say hi
because you were dating in secret.
But now,
everyone knows you're married.
Are you shy now that you're married?
We're keeping work
and personal lives separate.
You speak as if
your private life is pretty eventful.
Hey.
Do you guys even do it?
Stop it.
You don't do that with family.
You used to be so fired up.
Why does it die
once people get married?
You burn to death
if you stay fired up.
NEW MESSAGE FROM YEON
FROM GENERAL AFFAIRS
I'm meeting old friends from school
and will be home late.
Okay.
Oh, dear. I'm so sorry, Mr. Kwon.
- It's okay.
- I'm so stupid.
I'm really sorry.
Don't be. It happens.
Ms. Seon?
I'm coming, sir.
- Sorry.
- Go ahead.
- Cheers.
I'm loving this.
- Right?
- Jun-seo!
- Over here.
- He looks even better now.
- Long time no see.
- You haven't changed at all.
Sorry, I forgot to tell you
he was coming.
Don't worry.
It's been ages since we broke up.
It has been a while, So-young.
Yes.
You look just the same.
You haven't changed.
I'm not the same. I got old, right?
No.
You're pretty. Just like before.
- What's going on here?
- You're prettier now.
- You're just the same.
- I lost my appetite.
- Sorry.
- Pour me a drink?
Here.
Let's begin.
You can vote now.
FINAL RESULT
OF THE THIRD SURVIVOR
Why did his ranking drop?
Vote for the person
who stole your heart.
The mission benefit is too great.
BOYS II PLANET's first round
of the final global vote is now open.
BOYS II PLANET's final global...
Can I vote for the same person twice?
Log onto the BOYS II PLANET site
and click "vote"
- then select one participant.
- Who's that?
Hi. Let's have a drink.
It's been a while.
What are you up to?
Do you want to get back with me?
Do you want to?
Forget it, then.
Gosh.
You're really one-sidedly one-sided.
You asked me out
then suddenly ghosted me.
Now you barge in after two years
- and want a drink?
- So what?
Were you sad that I dumped you?
Did you cry over me?
You didn't.
"If you want to leave, go ahead.
I won't hold you back."
I bet you didn't even shed a tear.
Here. have a drink and call it even.
It's good, isn't it?
It's not bad.
Let me stay for a while.
- What?
- Let me stay here.
The whiskey's the rent.
This costs over three million won.
Hey, what kind of nonsense is this?
Get out. This isn't a boarding house.
I really don't have a place to go.
I had to leave my old place
and I couldn't find a new place yet.
You know that my family...
They're no help to me at all.
I get that you're in a tough spot...
You can't barge
into a guy's bachelor pad.
- I'll get you a hotel room.
- For how long?
Who knows how long I'll need?
Do you have ten million won?
I guess you can't help me.
I get it. I'll leave.
I'll stay at a sauna
or end up on some street corner.
And if a creepy guy hits on me?
I'll go with him. I can't be picky.
Goodbye.
It's only for the time being.
Leave as soon as you can.
I'll take the small room.
You can take the big room.
Wait, isn't that a given?
How brazen.
Take a look at the shower head.
It's leaking again.
Okay, I will.
You say that and do nothing.
Goodness.
Did you read about Zone F online?
Yes, I did.
Some people have too much energy.
They do something at work
that we don't even do in bed.
Shall we do it?
I'm tired.
I wasn't interested, either.
Turn off the light.
You do it.
You've lost weight.
Your face got smaller.
Are you stressed out
because of Joo In-a?
Drink the whiskey you brought.
Don't touch my beer.
Do you hate her that much?
Why?
Because she made you handle affairs?
They're PM cases, not affairs.
Ms. Joo doesn't know about me yet.
I was working on something
on Team One.
I put everything in the folder
and when she sees that
she'll see how good I am
and reappoint me.
If she's that competent.
Think about it.
She wouldn't want to waste
talent like mine on stupid cases.
Why not? I think
you're perfect for the job.
To handle the PM cheaters.
Why me?
- Hang on.
- You are
the best one for the job.
Hey.
That's exactly what Joo In-a said,
that I was the best for the job.
- Why am I best for the job?
- It's about couples in love.
- That's your expertise.
- What does she know about me?
We just met. She can't know...
No way.
That retreating figure...
Did she see me?
So the reason she chose me...
was that?
No, it can't be.
Can it be?
Is it?
Long, straight hair.
A white shirt.
It's practically a uniform.
I can't say for sure.
I don't think it was her.
Why were you staring at me?
Is a ghost haunting me?
I came to make myself some coffee.
You look like
you have something to say.
Mr. Noh.
If you have any concerns,
you can come to me freely.
Yes, rather than driving myself crazy
I'll ask her and clear the air.
- Ms. Joo.
- Wait.
I can't ask if she saw me kiss.
What is it?
What should we do
about the basement parking lot?
We've confirmed through our humint
that it's a real issue.
Shall we put up a sign saying
personal misconduct isn't allowed?
We can't say we did any work, then.
- We have to expose them.
- Expose?
How am I going to do that?
I can't go on a stakeout
just to wait for it.
A stakeout?
Why would you say something
so nonsensical?
We're not detectives.
Why would we go on a stakeout?
- Right, exactly.
- Exactly.
I heard that someone
on the Audit Team
flew a drone and took photos.
How could an auditor do that?
We're not some drone-flying club.
Down your coffee and get moving.
My poor legs.
This was the only company car
left for us to take.
Darn it. I should've brought my car.
Still, if you push the seat
back a bit
it should free up some space.
- No, it's fine.
- Let me help you.
It's fine, really. I...
I'm so sorry, Mr. Noh.
Jeez, what the heck
are we even doing?
Okay, Hyun-kyu.
You didn't do all that studying
for your degree
just to do this kind of job, did you?
Unlike you,
I didn't go to a good university
nor have great credentials.
I barely got this job
because I'm from the area
where Haemu built a huge factory.
Oh, during my interview I said
"White blood runs through my veins."
That's how I introduced myself,
and they liked how I was different.
- "White blood."
- White blood.
- By white, you meant Haemu's color?
- Yes.
That's why they call you
"White Blood Cell."
That's right.
You know, competent people like you
might feel bored
by what our team does.
But working at Haemu
which everyone envies
and being on the Audit Team,
the best team in the company
makes me pleased and proud.
Hey, White Blood Cell.
Yes, Mr. Noh?
I didn't doze off.
I was only blinking for a long time.
Do you remember
the day Ms. Joo first joined?
Do you know what she was wearing?
Just a moment.
- I remember such details perfectly.
- Do you?
See if you can remember.
What was she wearing?
She wore
black pants.
What about her top?
Her top...
It was black.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
It was black.
Or not.
I think it was a white shirt.
Hey.
Are you saying she wore white?
Maybe not.
- What?
- Was it black?
- No.
It was white.
Yes, white.
Why, you!
It was definitely white.
Am I mistaken?
Forget I even asked.
- I'll go get coffee, so sober up.
- Okay.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Gosh, what am I even doing?
So what if she saw it? I don't care.
It's not like I committed a crime.
Forget it.
Oh, my gosh.
Why are you so startled?
You walked in so suddenly.
Can't I walk in suddenly?
Should I have knocked?
What?
Were you
doing this again?
What was that?
So she saw it. She saw everything.
Noh Ki-jun.
What do you want?
You told me to ignore you at work.
It's just us now.
Is it Joo In-a again?
You look half-dead.
Yes.
Bury me on a sunny slope.
Why are you thinking
of getting buried?
You have a lifeline.
Director Kim.
His dinner with the VP got canceled
and he seemed to be looking
for a drinking buddy.
Hello, Director Kim.
It's Assistant Manager Noh Ki-jun.
Ms. Joo talks back
to every senior executive.
Does she think I'm staying still
because I can't speak up?
- I'm just keeping my boundaries.
- Yes, you're right.
Is she rude to the executives, too?
I guess she's not the type
to bow to the powerful.
I don't care how she treats
the powerful or powerless.
And there's you.
She has such
a poor judgment of character.
You're our ace, Mr. Noh.
Yet she dumped you in Team Three.
Now, you're handling PM cases.
What the heck is PM, anyway?
Exactly.
I'm having the worst time, sir.
Don't you worry about that.
You know who I am.
Let me tell you something
that's still off the record.
I'm working to create
a new department.
It'll serve as the control tower
of the whole organization.
Business General... No.
It's called
the General Business Control HQ.
General Business Control HQ.
- What a great name.
- Right?
I said I wanted you on the team.
You'll be able to escape soon.
- Let me pour you a drink, sir.
- Okay.
A toast
to our General Business
- Control HQ.
- Let's drink to its bright future.
- Cheers!
I'm in the mood.
I'm heading home.
Bye. See you tomorrow.
IT DEVELOPMENT TEAM
ASSISTANT MANAGER KWON HYUN-WOO
It's raining.
When do you get off work?
I'm working late.
Buy an umbrella and head home.
Hello?
Jun-seo?
We did that all the time.
Back then...
we were young and rash.
I'm glad I called you.
Are you sure
you don't need to eat dinner?
You love to eat.
I'm okay with anything
if I'm with you.
Right.
It's pouring.
- Why don't we...
- Yes?
stay together?
Just until the rain stops.
SEND
IT DEVELOPMENT TEAM, KWON HYUN-WOO
Sent.
Great work.
My gosh. You must be tired.
Great work until late.
Don't mention it. I'm feeling proud.
Today was
the first overtime of my life.
Really?
In that case
why don't we grab a drink
to celebrate?
I'd love to.
Let's eat
something delicious, Mr. Kwon.
- Okay, let's wrap up and leave.
- Great!
WIFE
I said you could leave first.
Were you rained on?
We shouldn't do this.
The rain has stopped.
Let's do it.
- What?
- Let's do it.
We can't keep going like this.
We have to do it.
What's with you?
All right. Let's go home first.
You're going to catch a cold.
Let's do it here.
It's that area. Zone F.
Hey.
- What's with you?
- Be quiet.
DIRECTOR KIM HAN-SU
The president approved!
You'll be out of the Audit Team
within days, Mr. Noh.
Director Kim, you're awesome!
I'm the best
- Are you getting off early today?
- I'll try to.
- Let's eat something good.
- Okay.
- Try to clock out quickly.
- Hello. Good morning.
- Hello.
- The weather's great, isn't it?
- Yes.
You're looking extra sharp today.
- Do I?
- Yes.
You two look great, too.
- Thank you.
Hello, Ms. Joo.
Hey, Mr. Noh. Good morning.
You must like dress shirts.
You look good in them.
You're looking happy.
Did something great happen
this morning?
There's no reason
to be in a foul mood.
Look at that great weather.
There is a reason, actually.
You haven't caught
a single case in the parking garage.
You won't take matters lightly
just like you did
with Mr. Son's case, will you?
Keep it up, will you?
Every assignment is important
here in the Audit Team.
Fine, I'll go along. I won't have
to see her for much longer.
Yes, of course.
I even brought my car
to stake out properly.
Will I ever let you down again?
No, never.
Ms. Joo.
There was a huge lucky draw
at our online mall recently
and people are asking
how the winners were decided
or if the draw was even real,
and some are complaining
that they didn't win
even after many tries.
It's not like the Audit Team
is the customer service center.
Mr. Noh, you can continue
to work on the parking lot case.
Wait a second.
You'll need a partner
for your stakeout, won't you?
Goodness. One second.
White Blood Cell is on the phone too.
We don't have enough manpower.
We do, Mr. Moo.
We have our strongest asset here.
Who?
You're making me feel uncomfortable.
Cut it out.
Why? Is the parking lot case
not quite suitable for you?
But you told me that every case here
is equally important.
Shall I do that, then?
Let's spend some quality time alone.
You don't need to buckle up.
I'm not starting the car.
It's my decision.
Come on. You forgot, didn't you?
Unbuckle it.
It must be uncomfortable.
No, I'm not uncomfortable at all.
I feel so comfortable right now.
Unbuckle it. You don't need
to play it cool over this matter.
Things happen.
Stakeouts are for people
who are experienced.
It's all right.
I knew it. Your understanding
of these assignments is very high.
Sorry?
I'm sure you know a thing or two
about cases like this one.
Ms. Joo.
- Back then, that...
- That? What do you mean by that?
That. Whatever it is you saw.
It wasn't that...
I'm not that kind of person.
My lips were also...
Quiet.
Over there.
Okay.
I'll wrap it up. It's my job.
I'll open the door.
I'm from the Audit Team.
I'm opening the door.
Oh, my. Director Kim!
You said you were busy.
- Wait.
- What are you two doing here?
What's with you?
You, of all people,
should know better.
When you both have spouses,
don't you?
Will you close that door?
Wrap it up and come outside.
I knew it, Mr. Noh.
I knew you could do it!
You caught a big one.
He's a big fish!
This is why you're the ace
of the Audit Team.
Let's see.
Director Kim was
formerly your direct superior.
You took down your former superior
whom you worked with for years
like a cold-blooded man!
If only everyone else were like you
this world would've been
a much better place.
Excuse me, Ms. Joo.
Is there a possibility
that Director Kim will be let off
- just like Mr. Son?
- No.
This is a different case.
He's an executive, so we can revoke
his contract and fire him right away.
Fire him?
But Director Kim is also
a necessary part of the company...
Not at all.
He's an old-timer with an ego
who sits around doing nothing
only because
he's close to the president.
He must've been an eyesore
to the vice president.
You just gave him
a wonderful reason to fire that man.
Director Kim
is done for.
DIRECTOR KIM HAN-SU
Your call cannot be connected.
You will be redirected to...
ELDEST SISTER
ACCEPT
- Hilarious.
- Hey.
Hello, Ki-jun? When are you coming?
I'm on my way, and I'm almost there.
Ki-jun, we have to change
the bathroom doorknob, too.
Okay.
Hey, Ki-jun!
Take a look at Jin-yeong's laptop.
- Laptop?
- Hey, Ki-jun.
That couch has been wobbling.
Take a look.
I'm only one man,
so talk to me one at a time.
The couch?
- Which side is wobbly?
- The left.
Goodness.
Goodness, I'm so proud of you,
my youngest one.
Cut it out, Mom.
Mom, this meat is delicious.
Hey, Ki-jun.
Why are you drinking so much?
Look at him.
He hasn't even eaten his food.
You can't even hold your alcohol.
- Stop drinking.
- Stop pinching me, please!
Will you just leave me alone?
Is something going on, Ki-jun?
Right? What's wrong?
Hey, is someone bullying you?
What? Hey, who is it?
Who's that punk?
Hey, go file a lawsuit.
- Talk to her husband!
- I'll talk to him.
We have to talk it out first.
Do you want me to make a call?
Please stop this and leave me alone.
We need the name first. Who is it?
- We have to talk it out first.
- Talk what out?
Look at this kid.
Call your husband first, okay?
Who's the punk that did this
to my precious son?
- You...
- Darn it.
- Who is it?
- Talk it out.
- Hey, tell me who it is.
- We need the name first.
- What's the name?
- Mom, listen.
- We need the name first.
- We need that.
- Who is it?
- Why won't he pick up?
- Get the name.
- We need the name.
You all need to stop.
- Who is it? Tell me!
- Hear me out.
- Ki-jun.
- I hate all three of you!
Just leave me alone!
No, bring her phone to me.
- Is he not picking up?
- Call the customer service line.
- The customer service?
- We need to reach someone!
HAEMU PHARMACEUTICAL
2025 CONTRACT INSPECTION
2024 FUND EXECUTION INSPECTION
NOH KI-JUN, AUDIT TEAM 1 TURNOVER
DO YOU WISH TO PERMANENTLY DELETE
ALL FOLDERS AND FILES?
I'm sorry about Director Kim.
- Did you dig him up intentionally?
- No.
It was a coincidence
from another case.
How disappointing.
I thought you finally learned
to wield your sword
but it was sheer luck.
I haven't given you anything yet.
Prove yourself
that you're different from your mom.
Honey, Sung-yeol is here.
You should say hi to him.
I'll go and make coffee.
Father, your youngest son is here.
- And so are you, Jae-yeol.
- It's been a while.
How's your health, Father?
I've exiled you
and haven't called you back.
How dare you show yourself here?
It's great to see
that you're the same.
How come there is
no middle ground between you two?
One of you is too soft
to do anything substantial
and the other is too reckless,
causing trouble everywhere.
Darn it.
You see, Father
I have caused yet another trouble.
It's the gas plant in Saudi Arabia
that you've even dreamed of.
I got the first package,
and on top of that the third one.
The entire project
is worth 8.77 billion dollars.
And I got it.
So? Isn't this good enough
to put an end to my exile?
I hear there's a spot open
in the head office.
Should I cancel the luncheon?
You do not look well.
I'm fine.
I need personnel evaluation reports
and a list of potential staff
up for a promotion.
Also, set up
a dinner with QS International's
President Lee Hyeong-geun
as soon as possible.
I understand.
Would you like to leave right away
for the AI camp?
In half an hour.
One second.
I can do this for myself.
E-mail me the files.
Yes, sir.
- What now?
- I'm telling you.
Goodness, I need some sugar.
My gosh.
Where was Ms. Yoon's snack box again?
There it is. Ms. Yoon's snack box.
Goodness. It's heavy.
Did you get something new?
Hey, these are new.
It's good.
- Mango-flavored?
- Yes.
Hey, Hae-young. Where are we
having team dinner again?
Piggy's Charcoal BBQ.
We're having pork again?
Can we get something better?
It's Ms. Joo's welcome party.
Our budget for team dinners
is running low this year.
Ms. Pyun.
Why do you act like
a stingy mother-in-law
who never lets anyone near her money
with the company fund?
There's a servant
that's trying to clean out the fund
so I have no other choice, Mr. Moo.
- What?
- Servant?
You heard her, right?
Did you just call me a servant?
- Do you feel guilty?
- Technically, we're all servants.
Anyway.
Where's Mr. Noh?
He's been away for a while.
Mr. Noh didn't seem well.
He doesn't look well,
he keeps sighing
and his eyes looked a bit watery too.
- Anyway, he looks quite sad.
- Really?
- Did he get dumped?
- I think so.
Goodness. That's heartbreaking.
Thanks a lot.
He is
leaving.
My hope.
My lifeline.
Adios.
PIGGY'S CHARCOAL BBQ
Hello.
Thank you.
It used to be a great spot.
Back then, the front of the factory
used to be salt farms.
It became a huge issue.
What's the most important
when it comes to making salt?
Sunlight and wind.
So if the southeastern direction
gets blocked off
it creates a shadow
and stops the wind
which stops salt from crystallizing.
And the one who stepped up
as a troubleshooter was...
Mr. Baek.
- You should eat some, too.
- I've been eating. It's okay.
You're making me look rude.
After all, I'm the youngest.
No, it's all right, really.
Because everyone thinks
you're just like that.
That I'm just rude?
That wasn't what I meant.
The meat is burning. Have some.
- And Mr. Oh is such an odd guy.
- You just dissed me.
This happened during the early days
of his time in China.
Really?
What do you mean?
I haven't said anything.
- I can't believe it.
- Wait, it's not that.
Will you listen up?
Anyway, this guy...
All right.
Audit Team Three,
why don't we make a toast?
Hello, Ms. Joo.
Thank you.
- Shall we have a toast?
- One second, please.
Goodness.
- Yes, drink up.
- I will.
We're all here
to make a living, aren't we?
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- Now, would you like a drink?
- Yes, Ms. Joo.
- Drink up.
- Thank you.
Mr. Noh, why don't you
have a drink, too?
You want soju?
Okay.
You've done well, Mr. Noh.
You all know
that Mr. Noh got someone big, right?
Yes, of course.
Mr. Noh is the pride of our team!
He says you're the pride.
Why don't we make a toast to Mr. Noh,
the ace of Audit Team Three?
- Shall we?
- Goodness.
All right.
To Mr. Noh.
- Cheers!
- All right, Mr. Noh!
That's nice.
Gosh.
That's a nice drink.
May I?
A lettuce wrap, Ms. Joo.
I need you baby, bye bye bye
Must you go, why why why?
All you said was a lie lie lie
I will wait
Until the day I die
Do not cry alone
Because I am not there
Goodbye
Come back
My dear
Do you not know
- These songs are killing the vibe.
- Right?
May I resuscitate the mood
as the head of this organization?
Drop that microphone now.
Come back here, Mr. Noh.
It's "Twit"!
Okay!
You're a fool
- Twit, twit, twit, twit!
I don't like it
Nobody likes it
The delicate Sim Cheong
- Twit, twit, twit, twit!
I don't like it
Nobody likes it
You're a fool
All you care about is yourself
The delicate Sim Cheong
Try to look around
You're in pain but you have no idea
You make me royal
You make me a hero
You make me a genius, yes
You give a lot
But why do you always end up unhappy?
Because you only breathe for yourself
You're a fool
- Yeah! Twit, twit, twit, twit!
- Twit, twit, twit, twit!
I don't like it
Nobody likes it
Ms. Joo In-a.
Don't you think this is too much?
Fine.
I kissed.
I know that's why you put me
in charge of PM.
But what's so bad about that?
Why is that misconduct?
Does anyone here never kiss?
Ever?
Don't you ever kiss?
Don't you kiss, too?
Are you okay?
You threw up all night.
I heard
you dropped a bomb last night.
How did you know?
We are a company.
Something fun like that
goes around in real-time.
You've never been
the object of hatred, have you?
You're the beloved Noh Ki-jun,
whom everyone liked.
Beloved, my foot.
After all, it's just work.
She'll forget someday
if I do my job well, right?
Ki-jun.
When you adore someone,
you adore them for no reason.
But once you hate someone,
you hate them no matter what they do.
I'm sure Ms. Joo thinks
you're her biggest eyesore right now
no matter what you do.
Should I just quit?
You still need to get to work
to turn in your resignation.
I'm taking the day off.
Good for you.
Excuse me, Ms. Joo.
I apologize for last night.
You must've been quite disappointed.
Sorry?
That you couldn't transfer
to General Business Control HQ.
You should've talked to me
if you wanted to leave the team.
I'm not that uptight.
Instead of talking behind my back.
Also, that department
is no longer in formation
with Director Kim's dismissal.
Are you feeling all right?
I think
you're really something, Mr. Noh.
If I were you,
I could never come to work.
Stop making matters worse.
I'm sure it's hard enough for him.
Isn't it?
I guess he's the type who blows up.
No, okay? That's not it.
NOH KI-JUN
CHECK SEVERANCE PAY
SEVERANCE PAY: 40,788,560 WON
All right.
That's enough money
to last some time to get refreshed
before I get another job.
Dang it. I'll just quit.
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
NAME: NOH KI-JUN
REQUESTED BY: NOH KI-JUN
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
Ms. Joo, I must talk to you.
Mr. Noh.
Mr. Noh!
Did you take my printout?
AUDIT TEAM 3 STATIONERY SPENDINGS
One moment, please.
Here.
Jeez.
YOU HAVE A NEW E-MAIL:
REPORTING MS. JOO IN-A
HEAD OF AUDIT
HEAD OF AUDIT JOO IN-A
REPORTING MS. JOO IN-A
MS. JOO IN-A IS INVOLVED
IN AN INAPPROPRIATE
WORKPLACE RELATIONSHIP
FILING FOR LOVE
GUEST APPEARANCES BY SHIN HYUN-SOO,
PYO YE-JIN, AND KIM JONG-TAE
Did I get you?
If that report turns out to be true
that means I'll have what I need
to take Joo In-a down.
- What?
- What is this?
The Older Women Hunter?
You need to stop, ma'am.
Please leave immediately.
Joo In-a couldn't possibly be
having an affair.
Has she ever come with a man?
Gosh, ten condoms?
Our company is about to see
the biggest storm in history.
What kind of person is Joo In-a?
Subtitles by Eunsook Youn
and Jennifer Lim